{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Sprinkler Repair Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"__cache./api/resource/task/40095/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40095,"taskName":"Lawn and Garden Sprinkler System - Repair","taskDescription":"Service a Lawn and Garden Sprinkler System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Sprinkler Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":230,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Lawn care front backyard organic","textMessagingName":"Repr Sprinkler","rolloverLongDesc":"Systems consist of buried pipes \u0026 sprinkler heads that pop up when in operation. The whole system is usually controlled by a timer.","rolloverShortDesc":"Repair, winterize, adjust, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Service a Lawn and Garden Sprinkler System.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Sprinkler System Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Sprinkler Head Repair","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":47,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Sprinkler System Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Lawn and Garden Sprinkler System - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Sprinkler System Project","urlName":"Lawn-and-Garden-Sprinkler-System-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Sprinkler System Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"yard, landscape, irrigation, landscaping, watering, water, sprinkler, drip, bubbler, valve","emcCategoryOid":-12047,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":407,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40095/":{"taskOID":40095,"originalTaskOID":40095,"setID":407,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1178,"questionDisplayText":"Problem description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select all problems you are having with your sprinkler system.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6377,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Time clock needs to be reprogrammed","answerDisplayText":"Time clock needs to be reprogrammed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6376,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Time clock isn't functioning properly","answerDisplayText":"Time clock isn't functioning properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4238,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No water to one sprinkler head","answerDisplayText":"No water to one sprinkler head","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4237,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"No water to one area of sprinkler heads","answerDisplayText":"No water to one area of sprinkler heads","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6867,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Water is running continuously","answerDisplayText":"Water is running continuously","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5984,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Sprinkler direction/spread needs adjustment","answerDisplayText":"Sprinkler direction/spread needs adjustment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5986,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Sprinkler head(s) need(s) to be relocated","answerDisplayText":"Sprinkler head(s) need(s) to be relocated","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6242,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"System needs to be blown out and shut off (Fall shut down)","answerDisplayText":"System needs to be blown out and shut off (Fall shut down)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6243,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"System needs to be reactivated (Spring activation)","answerDisplayText":"System needs to be reactivated (Spring activation)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5985,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Sprinkler head is broken","answerDisplayText":"Sprinkler head is broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1178,"questionDisplayText":"Problem description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select all problems you are having with your sprinkler system.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6377,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Time clock needs to be reprogrammed","answerDisplayText":"Time clock needs to be reprogrammed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6376,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Time clock isn't functioning properly","answerDisplayText":"Time clock isn't functioning properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4238,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No water to one sprinkler head","answerDisplayText":"No water to one sprinkler head","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4237,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"No water to one area of sprinkler heads","answerDisplayText":"No water to one area of sprinkler heads","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6867,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Water is running continuously","answerDisplayText":"Water is running continuously","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5984,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Sprinkler direction/spread needs adjustment","answerDisplayText":"Sprinkler direction/spread needs adjustment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5986,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Sprinkler head(s) need(s) to be relocated","answerDisplayText":"Sprinkler head(s) need(s) to be relocated","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6242,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"System needs to be blown out and shut off (Fall shut down)","answerDisplayText":"System needs to be blown out and shut off (Fall shut down)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6243,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"System needs to be reactivated (Spring activation)","answerDisplayText":"System needs to be reactivated (Spring activation)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5985,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Sprinkler head is broken","answerDisplayText":"Sprinkler head is broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6377,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Time clock needs to be reprogrammed","answerDisplayText":"Time clock needs to be reprogrammed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6376,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Time clock isn't functioning properly","answerDisplayText":"Time clock isn't functioning properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4238,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No water to one sprinkler head","answerDisplayText":"No water to one sprinkler head","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4237,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"No water to one area of sprinkler heads","answerDisplayText":"No water to one area of sprinkler heads","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6867,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Water is running continuously","answerDisplayText":"Water is running continuously","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5984,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Sprinkler direction/spread needs adjustment","answerDisplayText":"Sprinkler direction/spread needs adjustment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5986,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Sprinkler head(s) need(s) to be relocated","answerDisplayText":"Sprinkler head(s) need(s) to be relocated","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6242,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"System needs to be blown out and shut off (Fall shut down)","answerDisplayText":"System needs to be blown out and shut off (Fall shut down)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6243,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"System needs to be reactivated (Spring activation)","answerDisplayText":"System needs to be reactivated (Spring activation)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5985,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Sprinkler head is broken","answerDisplayText":"Sprinkler head is broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}